声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：傻瓜都一样  marjorie
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
已经没事了
You're okay.
深呼吸
Just deep breaths now.
呼吸
Just breathe.
呼吸就行了
你救她了吗?
Did you get her?
什么?
What?
有位女士  我正尝试着...
There was a woman. I was trying...
你救她了吗?
Did you get her?
救命!
Help!
我们得回到岸边去
We gotta go back.
救命! 救命!
Help! Help!
不用管我
Come on.
Jack!
那儿还有个人!
There's someone else still out there.
-Jack  或许你应该...  -她是谁?
-Jack, maybe you should...  -Who was she?
她叫Joanna
Her name was Joanna.
她本不应该在这飞机上的
She wasn't supposed to be on the plane.
前几天她在暗礁里潜水  后来耳朵发炎了
She was scuba diving off the Barrier Reef and got an ear infection,
医生叫她再呆两天
and so the doctor grounded her for two days.
所以她改了航班
She bumped her flight.
结果落得和我们一样的下场
That's how she ended up with us.
早上 她只是在游泳
She was just swimming this morning.
结果陷入急流里了
Got caught in the riptide.
在这已经有6天了 我却从没和她说过话
We've been here six days. I never talked to her.
我甚至一句话都没和她说过
Never said a word.
-Jack 不要这样...  -我们总共有47个人
-Jack, don't...  -There are 47 of us.
-我却一句话都没和她说过  -你已经尽力了
-Never said a word.  -You tried.
不  我没有
No, I didn't
我以为我可以...
I thought maybe I could...
我还以为我可以先把他救上岸 然后仍有足够的时间去救她
I thought I could bring him back and still have the time.
我就在那儿...
I was there... in the water.
水里面...
in the water.
我没有尽力
I didn't try.
我决定不去救她了
I decided not to go after her.
Jack?
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
你看到了吗?
Did you see that?
什么?
What?
有个男的  站在水里
Standing there in the water, there was a man.
你没看到?!
You didn't see that?
Jack  你最近一次睡觉是什么时候?
Jack, when was the last time you slept?
我得把这个和其它的工具放一块儿
I need to put this with the rest of the gear.
谁教你的?
Who taught you that?
那个韩国妇女
The Korean lady.
不要咽下去
Don't swallow it.
海水会越喝越渴的
Ocean water will make you thirsty.
为什么?
Why?
不要咽下去就是了 行吗 小子?
Just don't swallow it, man. All right?
看看你的嘴唇
你确实需要喝点水了
不 不用 我很好
谢谢
什么时候才会有人告诉我们要做什么
我认为不会有人来救我们
救援队很快就会来的
其他人...他们忽略了我们
如果我们尝试着努力沟通...
我们会获救的
我们不需要任何人的帮助
我会告诉你应该做什么的
你有没拿到?
Have you got it, or what?
你遮住了我的光  棍子
You're in my light, sticks.
-"光棍子"?  你到底在说什么呀?!  -光 逗号 棍子
-What the hell is that supposed to...?  -Light, comma, sticks.
你的腿和棍子一样苗条
As in those legs of yours.
听着 即使我很喜欢你给我起的绰号
While I love my new nickname,
-而且叫起来很好听...  -冷静
-and I think it's sweet...  -Calm down.
我拿到你要的东西了
I got your damn stuff.
能防止沙蚤叮咬?
It'll keep off sand fleas?
当然
You bet.
即使含有芦荟
Even has aloe.
多少钱?
How much?
钱在这儿没有用
Your money's no good here.
那你到底要什么?
Then what the hell do you want?
-如果你真认为我...  -5000美元
-If you really think I...  -Five grand.
你不是说钱没用吗?!
I thought you said my money as no good here.
我在协商
I was negotiating.
我可以接受"I.O.U"(我欠你一个人情)
I can take an IOU.
我有种感觉  你善于...
Something tells me you're good...
这样的事
...for it.
有没有看到哪儿有梳子?
You haven't found a hairbrush in there, have you?
没看到过  抱歉
No. Sorry.
老天  我已经翻遍20只行李箱了
God, I must've looked through 20 suitcases.
却一把梳子都找不到 太奇怪了 对吧?
Can't find one. It's weird, right?
我意思是 你一定认为每个人都带上梳子了
I mean, you'd think that everyone packs a hairbrush...
你没事吧?
You all right?
没事  只是有点发烧
Yeah, it's just the heat.
我...我怀孕了
Oh. And I'm pregnant.
是这样!
Really?
谢谢
Thanks.
你干什么呢?
What are you doing?
我正在把实用的衣物从没用的衣物中整理出来
I'm sorting the practical clothes from the impractical.
能帮忙吗?
Wanna help?
当然
Sure.
我可以...我可以问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you something?
当然  问吧
Sure. Shoot.
你是双子座?
Are you a Gemini?
-是 是的  -我说嘛
-Yeah, I am.  -I thought so.
坐不住  充满热情
Restless. Passionate.
你知道  大家都认为占星学是垃圾
Everyone thinks astrology is just a load of crap,
那是因为他们一点儿都不懂
but that's because they don't get it.
如果你愿意  我可以把你的星辰八卦算出来
I could do your chart if you wanted.
不愿意就算了
Or not.
双子座
Geminis.
嘿  Jack
Hey, Jack?
你看起来很疲劳  老兄
You look tired, brother.
我没事
I'm fine.
有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
就这些?
That's it?
就这些了
That's it.
-有多少?  -18瓶
-How many?  -Eighteen.
大家都还只拿了一点点  以为够用就行了 因为...
People just kinda took what they needed 'cause...
大家都以为救援队马上到...
we were supposed to be rescued.
但是没有
But we weren't.
如果把它们分了 即使每瓶水对半分
Even if we divided it up,
还是分不到47个人的
it wouldn't be enough for 47 people.
46个
Forty-six.
现在只有46个了
There's 46 of us now.
如果被他们发现只有这么点水了 他们会失去理智的
If people find out this is all we have, they'll freak out.
上次抓到的那只野猪快吃完了
The boar's running low.
-我们该怎么跟他们说?  -我不知道
-What should we tell them?  -I don't know.
或许我们可以做一些"找水棒"
Make water-finding sticks.
这些水怎么处理?
What should we do with what we got?
我不知道
I don't know.
放在帐篷里 行吧?
We should put it in the tent, yeah?
或许狗可以找到水
Maybe the dog can find water.
最好不要让大家知道这件事
Better if no one knows how little is left.
我是说 狗可以找到罐子和炸弹 那它也一定能找到水
Dogs can find pot and bombs, so I'm sure they can find water.
如果告诉他们东西都快吃完了 那我们就可以限量供应了
We tell the others we're running low, we can ration it.
-那么你决定该...  -我什么事都不会决定
-Then you can decide...  -I'm not deciding anything!
为什么不?
Why not?
想进来吗?
You wanna come in?
那么...
So...
告诉我 发生了什么事?
You wanna tell me what happened?
几个家伙打了Marc Silverman
A couple of guys jumped Marc Silverman.
但他们没有打你
But they didn't jump you.
没有
No.
今天有个小男孩过来就诊
I had a boy on my table today.
可能比你小一岁  我不清楚
I don't know, maybe a year younger than you.
他心脏很不好
He had a bad heart.
当时情况很糟
It got real hairy, real fast.
大家都等着你的老爸做决定
Everybody's looking to your old man to make decisions.
我能够作出那样的决定是因为...
And I was able to make those decisions because,
那天快结束的时候
at the end of the day,
男孩死了  接着...
after the boy died,
我就洗手  然后...
I was able to wash my hands
回家吃晚饭
and come home to dinner,
看着弱小的Carol Burnett一开始还笑着 直到我心痛
you know, watch a little Carol Burnett, laugh till my sides hurt.
我怎么能那么做 恩?
And how can I do that?
我意思是  即使我失败了
I mean, even when I fail,
但我怎么能这么做  Jack?
how do I do that, Jack?
这个担子  我承受不起
Because I have what it takes.
不要选择  Jack  不要作决定
Don't choose, Jack. Don't decide.
不要想成为一个英雄
You don't wanna be a hero.
不要想着自己能拯救每个人
You don't wanna try and save everyone.
因为万一你失败了...
Because when you fail...
你真的承受不起
You just don't have what it takes.
为什么不放开我?
Why didn't you leave me?
我在和你说话!
Hey, I'm talking to you.
-以后再说 朋友  -我本可以救她的
-Not now, man.  -I could have made it back.
什么  不回答是吧?
What? You're not gonna answer me?
我告诉过你放开我的
I told you to leave me.
你都快淹死了
You were drowning.
你应该救她的
You should've saved her.
我没能救她
But I didn't save her.
你也一样不能
And neither did you.
你以为你救我  就很高尚了 就是个英雄了?
You think you're all noble and heroic for coming after me?
我没事的
I was fine.
你不是这儿唯一知道该怎么做的人 知道吗?
You're not the only one who knows what to do around here.
这事归我管
I run a business.
谁叫你救我了 恩?
Who appointed you our savior, huh?
谁给你这个权利?
What gives you the right?
看着我!
Look at me.
我在和你说话!
Hey, I'm talking to you.
看着我  Jack!
Look at me, Jack.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
爸爸?
Dad?
你爸爸又走了  Jack
Your father's gone, Jack.
你听到我说的话了吗?
Did you hear what I said?
他走了  Jack
He's gone, Jack.
-他会回来的  -这次和以前不一样
-He'll be back.  -This time it's different.
我要你带他回来
I want you to bring him back.
什么?
What?
他已经两个月没和我说过话了  妈妈
He hasn't talked to me in two months.
是你两个月没和他说话
You haven't talked to him in two months.
相信我  他不会让我带他回来的
He doesn't want me to bring him back. Trust me.
让他朋友去找吧
Let one of his friends.
他什么朋友都没有了
He doesn't have friends anymore.
你怎么会这么想?
Why do you think that is?
他说的很对
He was right about you.
什么很对?
Right about what?
-你并不理解他所受到的压力  -我理解
-You don't understand the pressure... -I understand pressure.
Jack 求你了 你知道他会出事的
Jack, please, you know how he gets.
他不会...
He doesn't...
他不会照顾自己 你得追他回来
He won't take care of himself. You have to go after him.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能
I can't.
"我不能"?
"I can't"?
你没权利说"我不能"
You don't get to say "I can't."
自从你做了那事以后
Not after what you did.
把你爸带回来 Jack
You bring your father home, Jack.
他去哪了?
Where is he?
澳大利亚
Australia.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
那个孕妇摔倒了
That pregnant lady fell down.
-怎么回事?  -她刚刚摔了一交
-What happened?  -She just dropped.
一定是发烧引起的
It must be the heat.
-还有呼吸吗?  -我想有的
-Is she breathing?  -I think.
快 让她躺里面
Let's get her inside.
好的
Claire?
Claire  亲爱的  醒醒
Claire, honey, wake up.
Claire  能听到我说话吗?  Claire?
Claire, can you hear me? Claire?
快  醒醒  快
Come on. Wake up. Come on.
快  醒醒吧
Come on. Please, wake up.
快  Claire  能听到我说话吗?
Come on. Claire, can you hear me?
是我  Kate
Hi, it's me. It's Kate.
-什么?  -你刚昏过去了
-What...?  -You passed out.
不用担心  好吗?
Just take it easy, okay?
她需要水
She needs water.
-水  -不要动 好吗?
-Water.  -Don't move, okay?
天 太烫了 她发烧了
She's burning up. She's really hot.
亲爱的 我想你发烧了  呆这儿不要动 会没事的
Honey, I think you have a fever. You need to stay really still. It's okay.
没事的 没事的 放松
Just rest.
什么...
What the...?
水不见了
The water's gone.
被人偷了
Someone stole it.
医生哪去了?
Where is the doctor?
我不知道 大家都找不到他
I don't know. No one can find him.
那些是仅存的水了吗?
Was this the last of the camp's water supply?
是的
Yeah.
把水都放在同一个地方 怎么会这么蠢?!
Keeping it all in one place. Foolish.
我去丛林吧  看看能不能找到水
I can go into the jungle to find fresh water.
不要单独一个人去
You're not going alone.
要是被人发现水已经没了的话  会很难堪的
When the others find out the water's gone, it's gonna get ugly.
要是被他们知道水是被人独吞的
And when they find out that someone pinched it,
那将更加难堪
it's gonna get uglier.
我去找水吧
I'll go.
营地里需要你们两位 尤其是医生不在的时候
Camp needs you two here. Especially with the doctor gone.
而且 我知道去哪儿找
And besides, I know where to look.
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
你到底在哪儿?!
服务员说他已经三天没睡过这张床了
The maid says he hasn't used the bed in the past three days.
他有没向服务台借车?
Did he rent a car from the concierge?
没有 先生
No, sir.
坦白地说  Shephard先生
Quite honestly, Mr. Shephard,
我认为你爸根本没租借过车子
I don't think your father rented a car at all.
是吗?  这话怎讲?
Yeah? Why's that?
几天前 有人在这儿的旅馆酒吧闹事
There was an incident a few nights ago, here at the hotel bar.
我不得不叫保安送你爸回房间
I had to get security to escort your father to his room.
那和租车子有什么关系?
What's that have to do with renting a car?
-很抱歉 先生...  -说吧 和租车有什么关系?
-Sorry. I shouldn't have... -What's that have to do with renting a car?
Shephard先生 我认为悉尼的租车公司....
Mr. Shepherd, I don't think any rental agent in Sydney
不会借车给你爸这样情况的人
would lease your father a car in his condition.
我爸是主刀医师
My father is the chief of surgery.
当然 先生 我道歉
Of course, sir. I apologize.
他钱包落这了
He left his wallet.
谁会不带钱包呢?
Who leaves a wallet?
我想你还是报警吧  Shephard先生
Perhaps you should talk to the police, Mr. Shephard.
你到底在哪?
Where are you?
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
你没事吧?
You okay?
-我已经多久....  -几个小时了
-How long have I...?  -A couple of hours.
喝吧
Here.
水不多 但我们只能找到这些了
It's not much, but it's what we have.
放松就行了
Just relax.
你得照顾到里面这小家伙 是吧?
You have to think about the little one now.
谢谢你给我水喝 Charlie
Thanks for the water, Charlie.
要不是被哪个狗杂种偷了 水还会更多
There'd be more if some git hadn't nicked it.
-Jack回来了吗?  -没有
-Is Jack back yet?  -No.
没人看到过他
No one's seen him.
但用不着担心
But I wouldn't worry.
好好先生Locke已经去丛林给你找水了
Good ol' Mr. Locke's gone into the jungle to get some water for you.
很好  我们唯一的猎手能够搞到吃的
Great. Our only hunter's gonna get eaten
但这不能说明他也能为孕妇搞到水啊
just so he can get the pregnant girl some more water.
这我不担心 亲爱的  我意思是 你能告诉我...
I wouldn't worry. You tell me,
在黑暗的小巷里 你最希望碰到谁?
who would you rather meet in a dark alley,
不管出现什么 至少那老头有400把刀子?
whatever's out there, or that geezer with his 400 knives?
我意思是 谁会裹上400把刀子?
I mean, who packs 400 knives?
对我个人而言 行李箱内最多放上200-300把刀子
Personally, I can only have space for 200. Three hundred, at most.
他们什么时候来救我们?
When are they gonna rescue us?
快了
Soon.
谢谢你  Charlie.
Thanks, Charlie.
谢什么?
For what?
这儿的人似乎都不把我放在眼里
People don't seem to look me in the eye here.
我想我很怕他们
I think I scare them.
这个孩子  我就像个有责任在身的定事炸弹 就等着爆炸
The baby. It's like I'm this time bomb of responsibility just waiting to go off.
你不必怕我
You don't scare me.
那对中国夫妇有水
The Chinese people have water.
你哪里弄来的?
Where did you get this?
-你...哪里...弄...  -她听不懂的 Sayid
-Where did you get...?  -She doesn't understand, Sayid.
她能理解我的意思
She understands me.
是你偷的水吗?
Did you steal this water?
好了 大家和气点 行不? 有话好好说 好吗?
Okay, just take it easy. All right? We just want to talk. All right?
这本来有水的  是你的吗?
This had water in it. Is it yours?
谁给你的?
Who gave you this?
我没看到过水
I don't see the water.
那又如何?
And?
你追着他不放  他还是不会给你什么的
You go after him now, he'll give you nothing.
但如果你再等等
But if you wait...
兔子的尾巴总会露出来的
a rat will always lead you to its hole.
-时机终于来了  -干什么?
-Well, it's about time.  -For what?
四年前的生日上  我就许下了这个愿
I made this birthday wish four years ago.
水在哪?
Where's the water
这样好多了
This is better.
放开我
Get off of me.
快把水拿出来!
Give us the water now!
你要是再敢碰我 嗯?
Yeah, touch me again, huh?
还真以为是我偷的水?
You really think I stoled your damn water?
我们都知道你给了那韩国人两瓶水
You gave two bottles to the Koreans.
我没有给过任何人 任何东西
I don't give nothing to nobody.
不在这儿
It's not here.
我仅存的一瓶水和Miyagi先生交换鱼用了
I traded Mr. Miyagi the last of my water for a fish he caught.
我们以最"原始的"方式做交换
We worked it out caveman-style.
你把最后的两瓶水给他了?
You gave him your last two bottles?
水又没什么价值的 斑点女
Water has no value, freckles.
迟早会下雨的
It's gonna rain sooner or later.
嘿嘿  我乐观吧
And, hell, I'm an optimist.
你忘了样东西
You forgot something.
就当你是这儿新上任的镇长
Seeing as you're the new sheriff in town,
带这个会看起来正式一些
might as well make it official.
他们怎么样了?
How are they?
大伙们?
The others.
口渴
Thirsty.
饥饿
Hungry.
等着被解救
Waiting to be rescued.
他们需要有个人告诉他们该怎么做
And they need someone to tell them what to do.
我不能
I can't.
为什么不能?
Why can't you?
因为我不是个领袖
Because I'm not a leader.
但他们都把你当领袖了
And yet they all treat you like one.
我不知道该怎么帮他们
I don't know how to help them.
如果我失败了
I'll fail. I'll...
我承受不起
I don't have what it takes.
你为什么来这儿 Jack?
Why are you out here, Jack?
我以为我要疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
不  你不会疯的
Oh, you're not going crazy.
不会吗?
No?
不 疯子是不会知道 自己就要疯了
Crazy people don't know they're going crazy.
他们都认为自己清醒的很
They think they're getting saner.
那么...
So...
你来这儿干什么?
why are you out here?
追东西
I'm chasing something.
应该说是人
Someone.
哦  白兔子
Ah. The White Rabbit.
"爱丽丝奇境记"
Alice in Wonderland.
是的
Yeah,
"仙境" 因为我追的人
Wonderland, because who I'm chasing...
他并不在这儿
he's not there.
-但你看到他了?  -是的
-But you see him?  -Yes.
但就是找不到他
But he's not there.
如果我来找你  说同样的话
And if I came to you and said the same thing,
作为一个医生 你会给我怎样的解释?
then what would your explanation be, as a doctor?
我会说  这是一种幻觉
I'd call it a hallucination.
严重脱水和过度的压力导致的
Result of dehydration. Post-traumatic stress.
过去的一星期 我每天晚上睡觉不超过两个小时  就这样
Not getting more than two hours of sleep a night. All of the above.
很好 这就可以说这都是你的幻觉了
All right. Then you're hallucinating.
要是你不是呢?
But what if you're not?
那大家都有麻烦了
Then we're all in a lot of trouble.
我是一个普通人 Jack
I'm an ordinary man, Jack.
肉 土豆 我生活在真实的世界里
Meat and potatoes. I live in the real world.
我从不相信...
I'm not a big believer in...
魔力
magic.
但这个地方不一样
But this place is different.
它很特别
It's special.
其它人不想谈论 是因为它吓着他们了
The others don't want to talk about it because it scares them.
但大家心里都很清楚 都感觉得到
But we all know it. We all feel it.
白兔子是你的幻觉吗?
Is your White Rabbit a hallucination?
有可能是
Probably.
但要是这儿发生的每件事
But what if everything that happened here
都有理可寻 那会怎样?
happened for a reason?
要是你追的那个人真的存在 会怎样?
What if this person that you're chasing is really here?
不可能
That's impossible.
即使是真的 我们也不要说它是
Even if it is, let's say it's not.
要是我抓住他了 结果会怎样?
Then what happens when I catch him?
我不知道
I don't know.
但当我环顾这岛
But I've looked into the eye of this island,
我所看到的...
and what I saw...
是如此的美丽
...was beautiful.
等等 你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
多找些水
To find some more water.
我和你一块儿去
I'll come with you.
不 既然有了开始 你就应当弄出个结果来
No. You need to finish what you started.
为什么?
Why?
因为只有当一个领袖知道往哪儿走的时候 他才是个真正的领袖
Because a leader can't lead until he knows where he's going.
警察是在国王路口的巷子里找到他的
Police found him in an alley in Kings Cross.
经扫描显示 他的血液酒精浓度偏高
Our tox screen showed a blood alcohol content
就是说 像他那样体型的人 很可能会发生心肌梗塞
which, for a man of his size, probably brought on myocardial infarction:
相当程度的 致命的心脏病发作
a sizable and fatal heart attack.
是他
That's him.
直飞新加坡的125航班将于9:40起飞 请从14号门登机........
Oceanic Airlines, flight 125 nonstop to Singapore, leaving from gate 14...
不能放飞机上?你什么意思?
You won't put it on the plane?
很抱歉 Shephard先生 但我们的登机规定...
I'm sorry. Our policy is that...
是你必须有合理的文件说明
the body must have proper documentation.
-没有回旋的余地...  -没有回旋余地
-There is no latitude to...  -No latitude?
-没有回旋余地  -没有合理的文件说明...
-No latitude?  -Without the proper documents...
听着 你不能这么对我  我已经准备好走了
You can't do this to me. I'm ready to go now.
-或许用其它护送....  -不!
-Perhaps another carrier...  -No!
你听我说 好吗?
I want you to listen to me. Okay?
我需要你的帮助
Because I'm asking you a favor.
Chrissy  我穿着和你一样的西装 站在你面前
Chrissy, I'm standing in front of you in the same suit
这么穿 是因为我要去参加我爸的葬礼 我请求你帮我个忙
that I'm wearing to my father's funeral, and I'm asking you a favor.
我必须在16小时内赶到L.A.X.
In 16 hours, I need to land at LAX.
我必须得让灵柩通过海关 因为那儿将会有灵车等着
And I need that coffin to clear customs because there's gonna be a hearse waiting there.
我需要灵车载着我和棺材去墓地 为什么呢?
And I need that hearse to take me and that coffin to a cemetery. Why, Chrissy?
Chrissy 为什么我不能作好安排 带他回家 然后举办葬礼?
Why can't I bring him to a funeral home and make all the arrangements?
为什么我要这么急?是因为...
Why can't I really take my time with it? Because...
因为我必须得做好
Because I need it to be done.
我得尽快结束这一切
I need it to be over.
我只是...
I just...
我得埋葬我的父亲
I need to bury my father.
嘿  Claire
Hey, Claire.
-你哪里弄...  -嘘...嘘....
-How did you get...?  -Shh
你哪儿弄来的?
Where'd you get that?
这就是小偷!
Here's your thief.
-他把水藏哪了?  -我不知道
-Where'd he hide it?  -I don't know.
这杂种居然有三瓶水
This wanker had three bottles.
你为什么要这么做 小子 嗯?
Why did you do it, pretty boy?
我坐在帐篷里面
It was just sitting in the tent.
-Jack刚刚离开  -Claire会死的
-Jack just took off.  -Claire could've died.
我打算马上给她水的 但是我就是控制不住自己
I tried to give her some sooner, but it just got out of hand.
-没人懂我意思吗! -发生什么事了?
-No one would've understood.  -What is going on?
总得有人负起责任来吧  水已经供应不了多久了!
Someone had to take responsibility. It would've never lasted!
放开他!
Leave him alone!
已经6天了
It's been six days,
可我们还在等...
and we're all still waiting.
等着有人来救我们
Waiting for someone to come.
但要是他们不来呢?
But what if they don't?
我们不要再等了
We have to stop waiting.
我们得把事情想想清楚了
We need to start figuring things out.
今天早上  一位女士游泳死掉了
A woman died this morning just going for a swim.
他曾努力的去救她 可现在你们却围攻他一个人?
And he tried to save her, and now you're about to crucify him?
我们不能这么做
We can't do this.
只为自己着想的人是没有用的
"Every man for himself" is not gonna work.
该是组织起来的时候了
It's time to start organizing.
我们该好好想想  如何才能生存下去
We need to figure out how we're gonna survive here.
现在  我已经找到水了
Now I found water,
淡水 山谷往上就是
fresh water, up in the valley.
我会先带一队人上去取水
I'll take a group in at first light.
如果你不想来  那还可以想想其它办法
If you don't wanna come, then find another way to contribute.
上星期  我们中的大部分人都还是形同陌路
Last week, most of us were strangers.
但现在大家都走在一起了
But we're all here now.
天知道我们会在这儿呆多久
And God knows how long we're gonna be here.
如果大家不能和平相处...
But if we can't live together,
我们都会孤独的死去
we're gonna die alone.
谢谢
今天你把水给了我
那是丈夫应该做的
告诉我  那感觉如何?
So how's it feel?
什么感觉如何?
How's what feel?
在人人痛恨的名单之首取代了我的位置
Taking my place at the top of everyone's most hated list.
很不好受  是吧?
Sucks, don't it?
谢谢
Thanks.
今天去哪了  Jack?
So where were you today, Jack?
有些事  我不得不去解决
Just had to take care of a few things.
你就只能告诉我这些 恩?
That's all I'm gonna get, huh?
我父亲去世了
My father died.
在悉尼
In Sydney.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是的...
Yeah.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====